ILGWU Montreal Joint Board Records 5780/116
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor Legislation, 1942-1963 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- J.J. Spector, 1944-1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- J.J. Spector, 1949-1964 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- J.J. Spector, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Circulars, 1966-1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Circulars, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Circulars, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Circulars Authorization for Distribution, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Enquette - F.T.Q., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Enquette - F.T.Q., 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Enquette - F.T.Q., 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- St. Lawrence and Tributaries, Port Council of the Province of Quebec, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Complaints, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Travelers Federation of Quebec, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Travelers Federation of Quebec, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Travelers Federation of Quebec, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Lay-Away: Local 43, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Lay-Away: Local 43, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Local 61 Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Local 112: Lay Away, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Copies of Minutes: Local 112, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Cutters' Local 205: General Correspondence with Members, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Minutes - Local 205: Executive Board, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Minutes - Local 205: Executive Board, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Minutes - Local 205: Executive Board, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Local 205 - Cutters: Grievances and Fires, 1971-1976 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Local 207 - Invitations to Meetings, 1969-1977 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Trades - Cutters Local 207, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Local 262 - Grievance Meetings: Invitations and Reports to Members, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Local 262 - Invitations to Meetings, 1972-1977 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Copies of Local 262: Board Minutes, 1971-1977 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Local 262 - Minutes of Membership and Various Meetings, 1971-1977 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Local 262 - Welfare Funds, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Local 315, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Invitation: Executive Board Meeting - Local 315, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Local 342 - Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Local 422, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Local 421: Eastern Ohio, 1973-1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Local 422 - Invitations to Meetings, 1970-1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Local 438 - Lingerie and Undergarment Workers' Union, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Local 438 - Invitations to Meetings, 1969-1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Pressers' Executive Board: Copies of Minutes - Local 439, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Pressers' Executive Board: Copies of Minutes - Local 439, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Local 439 Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Pressers' Welfare Fund, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Copies of Minutes - Pressers' Welfare Fund, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Local 485, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Invitation to Meetings: Local 485, 1970-1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Local 521 - Granby, Quebec, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- New Guild Members (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Minutes of Labor Manpower, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Minister of Labour - Federal, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Forms - Re: Registration of Contractors (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Monthly Planner, 1972-1978 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Montreal Dress & Sportswear Manufacturers' Guild, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Montreal Dress and Sportswear Manufacturers' Guild, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Letters of District Council Convocations, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous: District Council of the Province of Quebec, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Guild Training Program (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Manufacturers' Council, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Local 205 Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Local 205 - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Local 205 - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Cutters Local 205 Copies of Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Dues Collections - Shortages, 1952-1954 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Joint Board - Annual Reports, 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Joint Board - Annual Reports, 1955-1960 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Joint Board - Annual Reports, 1955-1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Agreements: Embroidery, 1963-1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Local 262: Board Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Local 262: Board Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Local 262 - Welfare Fund, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Local 262: Welfare Fund, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Local 262: Welfare Fund, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Local 262: Shop Meetings, 1955-1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Local 262 Executive Board, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Grievance Committee: Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Office Employees Union, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Office Employees Union, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Office Employees International Union, 1950-1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Office Employee International Union, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Office Employees International Union, 1950-1953 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Office Employees International Union, 1955-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Office Employees International Union, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Copies of Minutes, Local 263: Executive Board, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Copies of Minutes; Local 263 - Executive Board, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Decrees, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Decrees, 1955-1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Decrees, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Decree, 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Correspondence with New York, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- News and Views, 1949-1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Labor Union Returns Act, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Joint Board Copies of Minutes, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Joint Board: Copies of Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Educational Committee: Copies of Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Mr. Bernard Shane - Trip to Europe and Israel, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Mr. Bernard Shane - Trip to Europe and Israel, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Justice, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Montreal General Executive Board, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board, 1958-1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board, 1950-1954 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board, 1948-1950 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board: Minutes of Meetings, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Affiliated Fashion Industries of Montreal, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Rainwear Manufacturers' Association, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Anniversary 1944 - 10th B. Shane, 1940-1949 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- B. Shane - 20th Anniversary, 1956-1954 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Shane, Bernard - 30th Anniversary, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- ORT, 1954-1963 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Banquet for Mr. Shane by Jewish Labour Committee, 1944-1959 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- David Dubinsky, 1959-1969 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- David Dubinsky, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- David Dubinsky, 1958-1963 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- David Dubinsky, 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- David Dubinsky, 1951-1956 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- The Midinettes, 1937-1962 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Local 521 - Gramby, 1965-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Canadian Coordination Conference, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Welfare Funds, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  December 31, 1966
- Annual Reports, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Imports, 1955-1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Imports, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Montreal Swiss Embroidery Works; United Swiss Embroidery Company; Springer Siwss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Montreal Swiss Embroidery Works; United Swiss Embroidery Company; Springer Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Montreal Swiss Embroidery Works; United Swiss Embroidery Company; Springer Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Montreal Swiss Embroidery Works; United Swiss Embroidery Company; Springer Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Montreal Swiss Embroidery Works; United Swiss Embroidery Company; Springer Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Montreal Swiss Embroidery Works; United Swiss Embroidery Company; Springer Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 17)